{
    "id": "20cca5cc6f354d8ebf0fbc8858aedee5",
    "title": "Sentence Completion Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I ..................... her since the day before yesterday",
            "description": "The present perfect is more common with the time expressions for and since.",
            "answers": [
                "didn't see",
                "haven't seen",
                "hadn't seen"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f9aadf2cb3bb441d8c5baa18acfa4146"
        },
        {
            "question": "Professionals ..................... nurses and teachers are often underpaid.",
            "description": "Either such as or like is possible here. Such as is more formal. ",
            "answers": [
                "such like",
                "as",
                "such as",
                "like"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "8d75ac32ed4b4d399971f64b1c242185"
        },
        {
            "question": "The girl ....................... sits next to Sam is his niece.",
            "description": "Use who to refer to people use which to refer to things. ",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "dd469837a0294d3ea7dc16b5951703aa"
        },
        {
            "question": "You …………………………….. do something to improve the situation.",
            "description": "Either should or ought to is possible here. ",
            "answers": [
                "ought to",
                "ought",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "66722f117801406e8c98ecb3e099ead2"
        },
        {
            "question": "You ......................... permit this.",
            "description": "Must is a modal auxiliary. Questions and negatives are made without do.",
            "answers": [
                "must not",
                "must don't",
                "don't must"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "afd77f864623488fa0813ff9d1ff9ac6"
        },
        {
            "question": "I opened the door but …………………... was there.",
            "description": "Not anybody means the same as nobody.",
            "answers": [
                "anybody",
                "nobody"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9249fdaa4fac4b68965f7183de3d84a0"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the sixth time you …………………………….. the same question.",
            "description": "The present perfect is common after this is the first/second/last etc. ",
            "answers": [
                "asked",
                "have asked",
                "had asked"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d6bb106806044207af4e00fd0620fc0d"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was a ……………………………. child who rarely spoke to anyone.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "quite",
                "quiet"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "be416fcdd51e4fc8b74e8d993f442a61"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is the ……………………………. girl in the class.",
            "description": "Chirpiest is the superlative form of chirpy.",
            "answers": [
                "most chirpy",
                "chirpiest",
                "most chirpiest"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cc873b60d6f84a75bbad4381ad947c9e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I failed the test …………………………….. I hadn’t prepared well.",
            "description": "Because is a conjunction because of is a preposition. ",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "because of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "999dc7b4a0b8405c9fd67456893bbbde"
        },
        {
            "question": "I worked ………………………. the best of my ability.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e40b8f803563440495522442ddb23046"
        },
        {
            "question": "He assaulted his brother …………………………… he was jealous of him.",
            "description": "Because is a conjunction. ",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "because of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "92f39e9a33744d68951238693b33dc96"
        }
    ]
}